National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty; Records apap298
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1972-2005, Undated; 3; 5 cubic ft.
  - Death Penalty Information Center, 2002 October (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Defense for Children International -USA, 1985 September-1992 April (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Delaware, 2005 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Delegation of Cuba, 2003 March (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Diminished Capacity, 2002 June (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Discrimination, 1991 June-2002 December (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Discrimination, 1991 June-2002 December (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Discrimination, 1991 June-2002 December (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Education, 1988 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Electrocution Packet, 1990 July (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - The Episcopal Church, 1993 February (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - European Parliament Meeting, 1988 June (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Evangelical Lutheran Church, 1984 March-1995 April (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Executions 100th, 1988 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Executions 200th, 1992 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Executions, 2001 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Exonerations, Undated (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Facts and FAQ'S, 1995 January (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Experts/Authorities, 1989 June (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Faith Based Organizations, Undated (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Families: Inmates, 1982 September (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Families: Victims, 1981 September (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Families: Victims Services, 1984 September (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Federal, 1989; 2000; Undated (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Federal Crime Bill, 1988 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Federal Crime Bill, 1989 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Federal Crime Bill, 1990 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Federal Crime Bill, 1991 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Federal Crime Bill, 1993 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Federal Crime Bill, 1993 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation, 1987 March (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Feminists For Life, 1992 October (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Florida, 1990 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Florida, 1995 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Foreign Nationals, 1994 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Furman v. Georgia, 1972 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - GLBT Groups, 1999 February (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Georgia, 1995; 1996 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Georgia, 2005 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Grigson - Dr. James, 2004 December (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Idaho, 2005 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Indiana, 1989; 1994 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Innocence, 1985 November (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - International Countries, 1994 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - International Declaration of Life, 1994 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - International Information, 2001 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - International Soering Case, 1989 July (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - International Standards, 1987 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - International Law, 2004 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - International - South Africa, 1996 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Juvenile Campaign, Undated (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Juvenile Campaign, Undated (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Juvenile Campaign, Undated (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Juvenile Campaign, Undated (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Juvenile Campaign, Undated (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Juvenile Campaign - Delaware, 2002 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Juvenile Campaign - Delaware, 2002 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Juvenile Campaign - Delaware, 2002 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Juvenile Campaign - Delaware, 2002 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Juvenile Campaign - Medical Research, 1986 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Juvenile Death Penalty Today, 1985 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Juvenile Death Penalty Today, 2000 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Juvenile Justice, 2002 October (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Juveniles - Arkansas, 2002 November-2003 March (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Juveniles -General, 2005 October (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Juveniles -General, 2005 October (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Juveniles - Idaho, 2003 November-2004 March (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Juveniles - New Hampshire, 2004 March (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Juveniles - Sentencing, 1999 January (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Juveniles - South Dakota [1 of 2], 2003 February (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Juveniles - South Dakota [2 of 2], 2003 February (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Juveniles - State Age Requirements, 1999 July (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Juveniles - Transfers, 1996 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Juveniles - Utah, 2002 November-2003 March (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Kansas, 2005 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Kentucky, 2005 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Law Enforcement, 1989 September (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Lawyers, 1990 December (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights, 2005 January (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Legislation, 1986 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Legislation, 1993 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Lethal Injection [1 of 2], 2001 September (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Lethal Injection [2 of 2], 2001 September (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Lobbying Information, Undated (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Louisiana, 1995; Undated (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Louisiana, 2005 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Maryland, 1993 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Maryland, 1997 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Massachusetts, 1995 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Medical Issues [1 of 5], 1990; 1994; 1996; Undated (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Medical Issues [2 of 5], 1994; Undated (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Medical Issues [3 of 5], 1987; 1989; 1990; 1993; Undated (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Medical Issues [4 of 5], 1999; 2001; Undated (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Medical Issues [5 of 5], 1999; Undated (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Mental Retardation, 2002 February (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Military, 1983; 1988; 1990; 1991; 1994 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Mississippi, 1991; 1996 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Mississippi, 2005 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Missouri, 2005 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Montana, 2005 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Moratorium in (IL), 2000 April (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Moratorium in (OK), 2001 January (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - NCADP Press Packet, 1992 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - NCADP Program/ Development, 2000 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - NCADP Media/ Communication Committee, 2000 July (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - National Committee, 1978 May-1990 June (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Native American, 1992 November (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Native Americans, 2002 January (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Nebraska, 1995 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Nebraska, 2005 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Nevada, 2005 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - New Mexico, 2005 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - New York, 2005 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Ohio, 1990; 1994; 1995 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Oklahoma, 1990 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Oklahoma, 2005 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - OP - ED Press, 1987 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - OP - ED Press, 1989 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - OP - ED Press, 1990 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - OP - ED Press, 1991 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - OP - ED Press, 1992 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - OP - ED Press, 1993 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - OP - ED Press, 1994 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Oregon, 2005 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Oregon, Undated (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Organizational History of the National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, Undated (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Papal Visit, 1987 January (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Pennsylvania, 1994; 1995; 1997 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Pennsylvania, 2005 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - People Against Executions, 1979 June (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Pharmaceutical Company Web Pages, 2001 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Pharmaceutical Information, 2000 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Photographic Documentation, 1992 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Physicians and the Death Penalty, 2001 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Pins, Texas Journey of Hope, Execution is Not the Solution, Execute Justice not People, 1988; Undated (Oversized 1)
  - Pro-Death Penalty, 1987 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Proponent Writings & Statements, 1989 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Prison Issues, 1997 October (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Private Prisons, 2001 October (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Public Opinion, 1989 February (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Public Opinion By State, 1991 April-1994 October (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Public Opinion By State, 1991 April-1994 October (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Racial Justice Act, 1990 July (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Religious, 1988 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Religious, 1988 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Report to the Executive Committee of the NCADP, 1981 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - S. 2869, 2002 July (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - South Carolina, 2005 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - South Dakota, 1994 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - South Dakota, 2005 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - St. Louis County Minority Clerkship Program, 1999 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Statements and Quotes, 1981 September (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Stop Killing Kids Campaign, 1996 July (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Supreme Court Justice Brennan, 1994 April (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Supreme Court Justice Blackmun, 1994 February (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Supreme Court Justice Ginsburg, 1993 June (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Supreme Court Justice Kennedy, 1991 November (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Supreme Court Justice Marshall, 1991 July (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Supreme Court Justice Powell, 1988 August (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Television Executions, 1991 May-1994 February (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Tennessee, 1995 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Texas, 2005 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Texas, 1994; 1995; 1997 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Texas, Undated (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - United Nations Commission on Human Rights, 2002 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - U.S Governors, 1999 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Utah, 2005 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Virginia, 2005 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Women on Death Row, 1998 October (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Workshop Survey - Presenters, Undated (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Wyoming, 2004 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Wyoming, 2005 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 53)
- Conferences, 1981-2005, Undated; 4; 0.55 cubic ft.
  Since 1981 the NCADP has held an annual national conference. Files in this series contain flyers, published materials, and documents from each conference. Also included is material from conferences held by affiliate organizations.
  - The Council of Europe, 2003 (Box 1 (4-Conferences), Folder 1)
  - Death Penalty Abolition Institute, 2003 (Box 1 (4-Conferences), Folder 2)
  - Death Penalty Awareness Day, 1987 (Box 1 (4-Conferences), Folder 3)
  - Death Penalty Forum, 2004 (Box 1 (4-Conferences), Folder 4)
  - International Human Rights Conference [1 of 2], 2005 (Box 1 (4-Conferences), Folder 5)
  - International Human Rights Conference [2 of 2], 2005 (Box 1 (4-Conferences), Folder 6)
  - National Conference (Photographs), 1997 (Box 1 (4-Conferences), Folder 7)
  - National Conference - Chicago, IL, 2002 (Box 1 (4-Conferences), Folder 8)
  - National Conference - Little Rock, AR (Photographs), Undated (Box 1 (4-Conferences), Folder 9)
  - National Conference - Nashville, TN, 2003 (Box 1 (4-Conferences), Folder 10)
  - National Conference - New Orleans, LA (Photographs, Undated (Box 1 (4-Conferences), Folder 11)
  - National Conference - Philadelphia, PA (with photographs), 1999 (Box 1 (4-Conferences), Folder 12)
  - National Conference - Raleigh, NC, 2001 (Box 2 (4-Conferences), Folder 1)
  - National Conference - Seattle, WA (Photographs), Undated (Box 2 (4-Conferences), Folder 2)
  - National Conference - St. Louis, MO (with photographs), 1998 (Box 2 (4-Conferences), Folder 3)
  - National Conference - Washington, DC, 1981 (Box 2 (4-Conferences), Folder 4)
  - National Conference - Washington, DC, 2004 (Box 2 (4-Conferences), Folder 5)
  - Northeast Regional Conference - New Haven, CT, 1988 (Box 2 (4-Conferences), Folder 6)
  - Student Death Penalty Conference, 2003 (Box 2 (4-Conferences), Folder 7)
  - Wrongful Convictions Conference, 1999 (Box 2 (4-Conferences), Folder 8)
- Petitions, 1999; 5; 0.75 cubic ft.
  Alphabetical
  Contains the Stop Killing Kids Petitions with signatures gathered from the United States, Canada, and Europe.
  - Stop Killing Kids Petition Binder - Belgium, Canada, United States [1 of 4], 1999 (Box 1 (5-Petitions), Folder 1)
  - Stop Killing Kids Petition Binder - Belgium, Canada, United States [2 of 4], 1999 (Box 1 (5-Petitions), Folder 2)
  - Stop Killing Kids Petition Binder - Belgium, Canada, United States [3 of 4], 1999 (Box 1 (5-Petitions), Folder 3)
  - Stop Killing Kids Petition Binder - Belgium, Canada, United States [4 of 4], 1999 (Box 1 (5-Petitions), Folder 4)
  - Stop Killing Kids Petition Binder - Netherlands, France, Spain [1 of 4], 1999 (Box 1 (5-Petitions), Folder 5)
  - Stop Killing Kids Petition Binder - Netherlands, France, Spain [2 of 4], 1999 (Box 1 (5-Petitions), Folder 6)
  - Stop Killing Kids Petition Binder - Netherlands, France, Spain [3 of 4], 1999 (Box 2 (5-Petitions), Folder 1)
  - Stop Killing Kids Petition Binder - Netherlands, France, Spain [4 of 4], 1999 (Box 2 (5-Petitions), Folder 2)
  - Stop Killing Kids Petition Binder - United States, France [1 of 3], 1999 (Box 2 (5-Petitions), Folder 3)
  - Stop Killing Kids Petition Binder - United States, France [2 of 3], 1999 (Box 2 (5-Petitions), Folder 4)
  - Stop Killing Kids Petition Binder - United States, France [3 of 3], 1999 (Box 2 (5-Petitions), Folder 5)
- Photographs, 1976-2001, Undated; 6; 1.95 cubic ft.
  Photographic prints of NCADP conferences and other events.
  - Aunt Mary, 1976 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - First Annual Meeting, 1978 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - Halloween party, 1979 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - Photographs, 1981 August (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - Andy and Bill, New Year, 1982 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 5)
  - Louisiana Execution of Joseph Cook, 1985 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 6)
  - Open House Pictures, 1987 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 7)
  - Bill Pelke Center, 1988 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 8)
  - Photographs, 1988 December (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 9)
  - Henry Schuwarzchild, 1989 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 10)
  - Camilie Bell, 1990 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 11)
  - National Pilgrimage, 1990 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 12)
  - Pilgrimage for Life, 1990 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 13)
  - Photographs, 1992 April (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 14)
  - Human Rights Day, Sydney, Australia, 1993 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 15)
  - Bill Pelke/Andrews, 1993 July (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 16)
  - Photographs, 1993 July (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 17)
  - Board Retreat, 1994 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 18)
  - Amgila Michelle Miller, 1994 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 19)
  - Photographs, 1994 May (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 20)
  - Photographs, 1994 August (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 21)
  - Photographs, 1994 September (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 22)
  - Photographs, 1994 October (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 23)
  - Azi Kambule, 1995 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 24)
  - Bryan Andrewmula, 1995 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 25)
  - Marin Youth Hostel - Muder Victims Family for Reconciliation, Journey of Hope, 1995 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 26)
  - Photographs, 1995 February (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 27)
  - Photographs, 1995 October (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 28)
  - Wilis Grove, 1995 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 29)
  - Heath Wilkins, 1995 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 30)
  - Rick Halperin, 1996 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 31)
  - Missouri Conference, 1996 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 32)
  - Photographs, 1996 January (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 33)
  - Blank Postcards, 1997 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 34)
  - Columbia Journey, 1997 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 35)
  - Journey '97, 1997 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 36)
  - Photographs, 1997 January (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 37)
  - Gama Baralla, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 38)
  - Capital Cards - Patrick Leahy, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 39)
  - William Lacy Clay, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 40)
  - Conference Workshop - St. Louis, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 41)
  - Tanya Cropper, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 42)
  - Father Pat Delahanty, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 43)
  - Jotaka Eaddy and Liletha Darideu, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 44)
  - Danny Glove, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 45)
  - Steve Hawkins and Danny Glove, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 46)
  - Marietta Jaegar and Helen Prejean in Texas, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 47)
  - Tonyo McClay, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 48)
  - Missouri Summit Meeting, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 49)
  - Missouri Summit Meeting, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 50)
  - New Orleans, Louisiana, 1998 June 19 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 51)
  - Photographs, 1998 July (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 52)
  - Postcard to Bill, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 53)
  - Texas, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 54)
  - Ron Tubak - Missouri Summit Meeting, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 55)
  - Rev. Reynolds Thomas and Ms. Vera Thomas, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 56)
  - Action, 1999 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 57)
  - Annual Conference - New Orleans, LA, 1999 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 58)
  - Annual Conference - Pittsburg, PA, 1999 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 59)
  - Annual Conference - Pittsburg, PA, 1999 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 60)
  - Annual Conference - St. Louis, Missouri, 1999 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 61)
  - Annual Conference - St. Louis, Missouri, 1999 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 62)
  - Annual Conference - Washington, DC, 1999 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 63)
  - Annual Fast and Vigil - Washington, DC, 1999 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 64)
  - Oscar Arias, 1999 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 65)
  - Harry A. Blackman, Supreme Court Justice, 1999 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 66)
  - Blue April, April Black, 1999 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 67)
  - Blue Individuals April 1999 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 68)
  - The Board at Work, 1999 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 69)
  - Board of Directors and Staff, 1999 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 70)
  - Julian Bond, 1999 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 71)
  - William J. Brennan, Supreme Court Justice, 1999 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 72)
  - Rosalyn Carter and Sister Helen Prejean, 1999 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 73)
  - Ruben Hurricane Carter, 1999 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 74)
  - Celebrities in Action, 1999 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 75)
  - Ernie Chambers, 1999 (Box 1 (6-Photographs), Folder 76)
  - Conference '99 Protest Rally, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - Contact Sheets, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - Mario Cuomo, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - Marshall Dayan, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - Steve Earle at Frankfort Rally, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 5)
  - Film Negatives, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 6)
  - General Photo Files, 1999 April (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 7)
  - Bianca Jagger, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 8)
  - Javeboo Hall and Jeff Garis, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 9)
  - Individuals (unlabeled), 1999 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 10)
  - International Abolitionist Movement, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 11)
  - Interns, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 12)
  - Journey of Hope - Murder Victims Families for Reconciliation, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 13)
  - Journey of Hope Tennessee, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 14)
  - Azi Kambule, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 15)
  - Celia McWee, Protest Rally, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 16)
  - National Activism, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 17)
  - Notes Found with Photographs, 1999; Undated (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 18)
  - Photo Negatives, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 19)
  - Photographs, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 20)
  - Photographs, 1999 April (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 21)
  - Pilgrimage for Abolition, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 22)
  - Pilgrimage for Abolition, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 23)
  - Sister Helen Prejean, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 24)
  - Claudia Roth, Chairwomen of the Committee on Human Rights and Humanitarian Aid of the German Parliament, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 25)
  - Diana Rust - Tiemey, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 26)
  - Symbolic Pictures, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 27)
  - Desmond Tutu, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 28)
  - Abe W. and Desmond Tutu, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 29)
  - Bad Welch, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 30)
  - George White, Bill Pelke, Sam Reese Sheppard, Abe Bonowitz, 1999 April (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 31)
  - Dennis Williams, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 32)
  - Youth Activism - NCADP College Tour, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 33)
  - Howard Zehr, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 34)
  - Chile Conference, 2000 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 35)
  - Gary Graham Execution and Funeral, 2000 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 36)
  - North Carolina Rally and March, 2001 (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 37)
  - Photographs, 2001 October (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 38)
  - Abolitionists Converged, Undated (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 39)
  - "Actual Innocence", Undated (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 40)
  - R. Adams, Undated (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 41)